Pinelands Folklife Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Field documentation arranged by fieldworker, Field photography descriptions are copied directly from B and C logs via Optical Character Recognition, so errors and abbreviations exist.
  - Carl Fleischhauer
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - Photographs of maps and drawings used in publications, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CCF84-001; Carl Fleischhauer; PFP-84-CCF-001; 21 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        All Frames: Photographs of maps and drawings used in publications
      - Railbirding on the Patuxent River, Jug Bay, Maryland, September 6, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CCF84-002; Carl Fleischhauer; PFP-84-CCF-002; 16 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, James P. Owings in aluminum Jon boat. Behind him, 50 year old plywood railbird skiff and fiberglass Barnegat Bay sneak box. G. Parsons, AFC, on dock; 2, G. Parsons, AFC, in sneakbox; 3, Owings towing skiff upriver; 4, Frank Astemborski, Delanco, NJ, in his NJ style railbird skiff. notice shotgun stand used for pushing solo; 5, 6, 10, 11, Wild rice zinzinia; 7-9, Owings pushing Astemborski; 12-16, Astemborski pushing Owings
      - Railbirding on the Patuxent River, Jug Bay, Maryland, September 6, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CCF84-003; Carl Fleischhauer; PFP-84-CCF-003; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, James P. Owings towing his Patuxent River style skiff with aluminum Jon boat with 5 hp outboard; 2-3, G. parsons, AFC and Paula J. Johnson in Parsons' fiberglass sneakbox with 7.5 hp outboard towing CF in NJ railbird skiff (Not Visible); 5-6, Owings jonboat. Frank Astemborski's shotgun stand stored in bow; 7-12, owing's (blue) and Astemborski (orange) in Owing's plywood Patuxent River skiff; 13-20, Ditto in Astemborski's NJ style skiff
      - Railbirding on the Patuxent River, Jug Bay, Maryland, September 6, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CCF84-004; Carl Fleischhauer; PFP-84-CCF-004; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-2, Sora Rail in bow of boat; 3-5, Frank Astemborski, Delanco, NJ railbirder; 6-7, Jim Owings, Rockville, MD, railbirder interviewed by Paula Johnson; 8-9, G. Parsons, AFC manuvering fiberglass sneakbox to dock at Jackson Landing; 10-14, F. Astemborski pushing G. Parsons in FA's N.J design rail bird skiff; 15-17, Small bag of sora rail at Jackson Landing; 18-19, Owings with railbirds
  - Mary Hufford
    - Field notes
      - Field notes, Mary Hufford; 65 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 13/120)
    - Field recordings on audiocassette
      - A log (audiocassette log), Mary Hufford; 155 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 13/121)
      - Interview with Ted Ramp and Marie Ramp, part 1, February 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23855; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-001; RYA 4818; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Heidelberg Avenue; 12GT
      - Interview with Ted Ramp and Marie Ramp, part 2, February 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23855; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-002; RYA 4818; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Tour of Lebanon State Park with Earl Danley, State Ranger, New Jersey, September 16, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23857; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-003; RYA 4819; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT
      - Tour of Lebanon State Forest with Christian Bethmann, Head Ranger, Lebanon State Forest, Route 72, New Lisbon, New Jersey, September 16, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23858; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-004; RYA 4820; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Tour of Lebanon State Forest with Superintendent Chris Bethmann, New Lisbon, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23859; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-005; RYA 4821; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Tour of Lebanon State Forest and outlying sites with local couple, New Lisbon, New Jersey, September 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23860; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-006; RYA 4822; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Tour of Lebanon State Forest with Norman Taylor and Caroline Taylor, New Lisbon, New Jersey, September 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23861; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-007; RYA 4823; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Lacey Township zoning officer, Richard, Gille, New Jersey, September 23, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23862; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-008; RYA 4824; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Lacey; 49GT Township
      - Interview with Mrs. Walter Hitchner, Brad Thompson, Flora Bozarth Beebe, Alva Thompson Ware, and Helen Ware Zelly, Vincentown, New Jersey, part 1, November 13, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23863; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-009; RYA 4825; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Vincentown; 23GT
      - Interview with Mrs. Walter Hitchner, Brad Thompson, Flora Bozarth Beebe, Alva Thompson Ware, and Helen Ware Zelly, Vincentown, New Jersey, part 2, November 13, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23864; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-010; RYA 4826; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Mid Green, New Jersey, part 1, November 14, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23865; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-011; RYA 4827; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Four Mile Circle; 27GT
      - Interview with Mid Green, New Jersey, part 2, November 14, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23866; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-012; RYA 4828; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Mid Green, New Jersey, part 3, November 14, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23867; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-013; RYA 4829; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Lunch and breadmaking with Leo Landy, Hazel Landy, Melissa Ramp, and Leo Landy, Jr., Nesco, New Jersey, November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23868; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-014; RYA 4830; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
        G-Nesco; 26GT
      - Interview with Mark Darlington, J.J. White Cranberry Company, Whitesbog, New Jersey, November 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23869; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-015; RYA 4831; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Whitesbog; 21GT
      - Interview and walking tour of place with Mark Darlington, J.J. White Cranberry Company, Whitesbog, New Jersey, November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23870; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-016; RYA 4832; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Russian Orthodox radio program, Dallas, Pennsylvania, part 1, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23871; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-017; RYA 4833; 1 audiocassette (60 minute); English, Russian
        G-Cassville; 48GT. Performer: Reverend William "Basil" Stroyen
      - Unidentified commercial recording of Russian choral music, between 1983 and 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23872; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-018; RYA 4834; 1 audiocassette (90 minute); Russian, English
      - Russian Orthodox radio program, Dallas, Pennsylvania, part 2, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23873; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-019; RYA 4835; 1 audiocassette (90 minute); English, Russian
      - Recording session of Merce Ridgway and the Pinehawkers, New Jersey, part 3, November 20, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23874; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-020; RYA 4836; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
        G-Waretown; 53GT. Performers: Merce Ridgway, Glenn Borden, Russ Horner, Arlene Ridgway, Leonard Gille
      - Meeting with Concerned Citizens, Medford Township, New Jersey, part 1, November 13, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23875; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-021; RYA 4837; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
        G-Cedar Run Wildlife Refuge; 18GT. Interviewees: Elizabeth Woodford, Elizabeth Wendt, Georgia Wurster
      - Meeting with Concerned Citizens, Medford Township, New Jersey, part 2, November 13, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23876; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-022; RYA 4838; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Mushroom hunting; Interview with the proprietress of the Copper Kettle, Cassville, New Jersey, November 13, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23877; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-023; RYA 4839; 1 audiocassette (90 minute); English, Ukrainian
        G-Cassville; 48GT. Interviewees: Eudokia "Dusia" Tserbotarew, Boris Weintraub
      - Visit to Harmony Gun Club, Sewell, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23878; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-AMH-024; RYA 4840; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Chatsworth; 27GT. Interviewees: L.B. Carpenter Sr., Larry Brickner, Charlie Pye
      - Interview with Herbert Misner, Betty Gravinese, and Lou Gravenise regarding snapping turtles, Medford, New Jersey, part 1, April 11, 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24083; Mary Hufford; PFP-85-AMH-001; RYA 4912; 1 audiocassette (60 minute); Rita Zorn Moonsammy
      - Interview with Herbert Misner, Betty Gravinese, and Lou Gravenise regarding snapping turtles, Medford, New Jersey, part 2, April 11, 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24084; Mary Hufford; PFP-85-AMH-002; RYA 4913; 1 audiocassette (90 minute); Rita Zorn Moonsammy
      - Interview with Hurley Conklin, Manahawkin, New Jersey, April 11, 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24085; Mary Hufford; PFP-85-AMH-003; RYA 4914; 1 audiocassette (60 minute); Rita Zorn Moonsammy
    - Field photography on black-and-white film
      - B log (black-and-white photo log), July 8, 1999, Mary Hufford; 21 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller); Reprinted from askSam database 07/08/1999 (Box-folder 14/122)
        See also Hufford, Mary--B/W contact sheets in Field Project Reference File in Reading Room
      - Menhadden Charity Singing, Port Norris, New Jersey; Decorative plant shed, Nesco, New Jersey, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 206230; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-206230; 33 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Bill Teitler
        5, Robert Lee Hamon, Oliver Johnson, Oliver Johnson, Robert Ames, Alexander Davis; 6, Oliver Johnson, Robert Ames; 7-9, Alexander Davis; 10, Oliver Johnson; These photos by Bill Teitler: 11-32, Leo Landy & Hazel Landy in decorative plant curing shed; 16, Sweet everlasting Anaphail Margotitoce; 17, Cat's paws Teriophora; 18, Baby Cattails typhus; 24, Bayberry Myrica Cerifera; 25, Grapevine wreaths; 32-36, Ted Ramp.
      - Four-wheeling at Hidden Lakes, New Jersey, September 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 215421-03; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-215421-03; 32 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Jay Orr
        1-3, Jay Orr, archival consultant to the project, with fieldworker Nora Rubinstein in the "Kaypro Room" at project headquarters, G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT; 4, Fieldworker Jens Lund, rigged for stereo field recording with a Nagra, outside the back door of project headquarters; 5-12, A truck, stalled in its effort to cross the lake, is pulled out by another vehicle and a strong rope. (Shot by Jay Orr) G-Hidden Lakes; 52GT; 13, Spectators at the event; 14-18, More shots of the stalled truck and efforts to help it out; 19-22, Fieldworker Mary Hufford interviewing Dave Dens bower and Chris Loveland, members of the Lower Bucks County (Pennsylvania) All Terrain Vehicles Club. (see PFP-83-RMH-006); 23, Spectators on the hill; 24-27, Nevin Ianuzzi making it across the lake and back in his Ford Bronco. Nevin Ianuzzi with Mary Hufford in (27); 28-31, More general shot?; 32, The trash pile. Because it is private property and the activity is quasi-legal, they aren't allowed to have trash barrels there. (?) So they pile all the trash in one spot.
      - Four-wheeling at Hidden Lakes, New Jersey, September 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 215421-05; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-215421-05; 26 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        Four-wheeling at G-Hidden Lakes; 52GT; 1, Fieldworker Jay Orr interviewing Bob York; 2-26, General shots of the event. Note Nevin Ianuzzi getting pulled out, (13-15) after his fourth trip into the lake. Spectators leaning on the truck that pulled him out. (16-19)
      - Places in Lebanon State Forest and Browns Mills, New Jersey, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 215594-03; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-215594-03; 31 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        1, USGS Topo Map, Brown's Mills quadrangle, identifying site of photos of G-Reeves' Bogs; 21GT; 2-11, Shots of Reeves' Bogs, prior to harvest; 12, Italian fellow showing mushrooms he'd picked near Shinn's Branch Road in G-Lebanon State Forest; 21GT. He declined to give his name; 13-14, Lebanon State Forest map, showing sites for Beaver Bridge at South Branch, and Five Points, an intersection of five roads, commonly referred to by foxhunters in the area; 15, Five Points; 16-31, Shots of Eugene's Oriental Food and Gift Shop. Kimberly Eandhait shown in (28-31). G-Browns Mills; 21GT
      - Children of Lebanon Lakes "popping wheelies" in Lebanon State Forest, New Jersey; House at Reeves' Bogs where Emmonses live; Cranberry cleaning machines, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 216448-04; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-216448-04; 18 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        1-6, Children of Lebanon Lakes "popping wheelies" in state forest; 7-13, House at Reeves' Bogs where Emmonses live; 17-21, Cranberry cleaning machines.
      - Interview with Valia Petrenko; Shots of yard decorations on Route 530, Browns Mills; Shots of yardscape, Browns Mills, New Jersey, October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 216898-01; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-216898-01; 36 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Rita Zorn Moonsammy
        1-5, Balloon headed effigy, along Route 530, G-Brown 's Mills; 21GT; 6, Pinelands Folk life Project Fieldworker Rita Moonsammy at headquarters in G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT; 7-9, Icons on walls of bedroom (at Valia Petrenko's house in Allentown--SS). Flash not in sync with shutter speed; 10, Kitchen. Painting of Last Supper draped with traditionally embroidered towel; 11, Fieldworker Rita Moonsammy with Valia Petrenko; 12-16, Valia Petrenko (a member of St. Vladimir's Russian Orthodox Church in G-Cassville; 48GT.); 17, Wall decorations in dining room. Note wooden mushrooms; 18-19, Text of Russian Orthodox mass in Syrilic. (sp?); 20-21, Valia discussing clump of earth brought from Russia for burial; 22, Harry Payne and his wife Gladys. G-Whiting; 52GT; 25-36, Shots of Taylors: yard. Note beagle graves in 25 & 26. Dog pens, 28-29, for fox hounds; mailbox with fox decal, 36. G-Browns Mills; 21G
      - Steven Lee III, Abbott Lee, Steven Lee, Jr., New Jersey, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217770-06; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-217770-06; 36 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Malachi O'Connor
        2-5, Steven Lee, III; Abbott Lee, Steven Lee, Jr.; 6a, Abbott Lee; 7a, Steven Lee, Jr.; 8, Boris Weintraub; 9a, Mal O'Connor; 10a, Abbott Lee; 11a, Steven Lee, III; 12a, ibid; 13a, Same as 1-5; 14a, Steven Lee, Jr., Boris Weintraub, Mal O'Connor; 15a, Steven III, Abbott, Steven Jr., Boris Weintraub, Mal O'Connor (in Mirror); 16a, Painting flanked with cranberry scoops; 17a-19a, Steven Jr., with granddaughter, & with Abbott; 20-36a, Exterior shots of house and surrounding land
      - Mass and graveside Service, Saint Mary's Russian Orthodox, Cassville, New Jersey, November 20, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217992-27; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-217992-27; 38 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        0-1, Graveside service following the mass, Father Stroyen and his wife in the center; 2, St. Mary's Russian Orthodox Church G-Cassville; 48GT from the cemetery; 3-4, Graveside bread being distributed and eaten; 7-8, Tombstone with photographs of deceased; 9-10, Mrs. G. Harkaway tending the graves of her husband and father; 11-13, More tombstones; 14-19, Mrs. Harkaway, tending the graves; 21-27, House with transplanted birch trees in front of it, G-CassvllIe, 48GT; 28-31, The Pinehawkers: Leonard Gille, ? Horner, Arlene Ridgway, Merce Ridgway, Russ Horner, Lenore Weisman, Glenn Borden. G-Waretown; 53GT; 32, Russ Horner, Lenore Weisman; 33, Arlene Ridgway, Merce Ridgway; 34, same; 35, Leonard Gille, Arlene's son by a previous marriage; 36-37, ? Horner (Russ's Brother)
      - Lunch with Leo Landy and Hazel Landy, Nesco, New Jersey, November 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217994-01; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-217994-01; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Brian Griggsby
        G- Nesco; 26GT; 6-12, Leo Landy carving ham while granddaughter looks on; 13, Hazel Landy in foreground with table set for lunch; 14, Leo placing ham on the table; 15-18, Leo in back yard with dog.
      - Chinese checkers game at the Taylors, Browns Mills, New Jersey, November 20, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 218076-01; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-BMH-218076-01; 3 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        1-2, Chinese Checker game in Caroline Taylor's kitchen, with daughter Jane, granddaughter Jennifer, and grandson; 3, Caroline Taylor holding grandson. Son-in-law in background. G-Browns Mills; 21GT.
      - Fieldwork for exhibit, Manahawkin, New Jersey; Delmont, New Jersey; Browns Mills, New Jersey, 1986, AFC 1991/023: 248521-01; Mary Hufford; PFP-86-BMH-248521-01; 17 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        1-2, Ed Hazelton, Manahawkin, NJ; 3-5, Linwood Veach, Sr. Delmont, NJ; 6-8, Veach Family; 9-13, "Trapper, Endangered Species" sign; 14-17, Norman Taylor's King dog, Browns Mills, NJ
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - C log (color photo log), Mary Hufford; 30 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 14/123)
      - Visit to salt hay ropemaker, Owen Carney, of Port Norris, New Jersey, November 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-001; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-001; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-4, Salt Hay mounded up outside of the workshed on Carney's property. G-Port Norris; no codeGT; 5-8, Carney, twisting salt hay into rope, aided by his ropemaking machine; 9, Carney's son, bringing the salt hay (Spartina sp.) in through the back door; 10-11, Carney and his son test the strength of the rope by pulling on it in tug-of-war fashion; 12-16, Carney with spools of the rope; 17-18, Fieldworker Rita Moonsammy photographs Owen Carney making the rope; 19-20, More shots of the outside of the shed
      - Interview of Joe Albert, Waretown, New Jersey, August 20, 1982, AFC 1991/023: CMH-002; Mary Hufford; PFP-82-CMH-002; 16 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Waretown; 53GT; 1, Shot of Joe Albert's dog kennels, used to house foxhounds and rabbit dogs; 2, Shot of the homestead, kennels in foreground; 3, Shot of dog house with summer home (dugout), taken from porch where Albert often sits; 4, The kennels again. He positioned them so they could see the house, especially the porch; 5, Albert reading from his log, a collection of notes and poetry, kept by him for forty years; 6-10, The journal, with excerpts. (The taped interview contains complete poems.); 11-12, Pawprint of beloved foxdog, Hector; 13,14,18, scenes from the porch; 15-17, Albert reading; 16, The home place
      - Four-wheeling at Hidden Lakes, New Jersey, September 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-003; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-003; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Hidden Lakes; 53GT; 1, No name gathered, referred to throughout the tapes by various people as "the kid," one of the youngest, and apparently the best "three-wheelers."; 2, Truck mired. Notice two tiered audience, and the kid in the background; 3, Mud spattered bystander; 4, same; 5-12, Three-wheelers churning up the perimeter, one goes through the center; 13, Spectators; 14, Mrs. Ianuzzi, making pictures; 15-20, General shots of audience and a truck going through the center. recreation
      - Four-wheeling at Hidden Lakes, New Jersey, September 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-004; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-004; 13 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Hidden Lakes; 53GT; 1, Four-wheel drive vehicles wrecked on the shore of the lake created by a sand and gravel mining operation, known as Hidden Lakes, near Pasadena; 2-13, Various scenes (see PFP-83-RMH-006-007 for details); 6, Mrs. Nevin Ianuzzi making pictures of her husband and his Ford Bronco; 7, Rob Stanley, being interviewed by Jay Orr. recreation
      - Interview of kids using Lebanon Forest, and tour of their forts, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-005; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-005; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Gary Moskos, hammer in hand, repairing the slingshot on the roof of his fort. G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT; 2, Gary Moskos and Paul Shrader, with their fort; 3, Same; 4-8, Same, on the inside; 9, Peter Boden; 10, Frank Day; 11, Same; 12-14, Peter Boden, displaying hognosed snakeskin that Freeman Taylor taught him how to cure; 15, Peter Boden and Frank Day; 16, Paul Shrader; 17, Gary Moskos; 18, Peter Boden, Frank Day, Paul Shrader and Gary Moskos; 19, Same; 20, Frank and Peter's fort, in the woods. children, games
      - Interview of four boys who live in Lebanon Lakes, about their use of Lebanon State Forest, and a tour of their forts, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-006; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-006; 16 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT; 1, The boys assembled near the fort built by Peter and Frank in the woods; 2, same; 3, same; 4, Cutaway view of same fort (cutaway is unintentional: the result of vandalism by little kids who aren't allowed to be there). The couch was furnished by someone's parents; 5, same; 6, The same four boys surveying the ruins of a much older fort; 7, same; 8, Paul Shrader; 9, Gary Moskos, Frank Day, Peter Boden; 10, Paul Shrader, Gary Moskos; 11-13, Peter Boden showing sassafras root to the other three. 14-16, Popping wheelies, on bicycles. children, games
      - Places in Lebanon State Forest, New Jersey, September 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-007; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-007; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        In Lebanon State Forest; 1, G-Reeves' Bogs; 21GT and surrounding area on topo map; 2, Cranberries in ditch surrounding Reeves' bogs; 3, View across bog from southwest corner; 4-5, Same as 2; 6-10, Same as 3; 11, Sphagnum moss (cal led sheet moss by Jack Cervetto) growing along road/path to bog; 12. Mushrooms gathered by an Italian fellow from Toms River who refused to give his name. He had participated in a homeowners woodcutting program two years ago where he was permitted to cut oak in a section of Lebanon Forest along Shinn's Branch Road. These mushrooms grow on oak stumps that have been dead for several years, and he knew they would be here after a rain; 13, G-Beaver Bridge; 21GT on G-Lebanon State Forest; 21GT map; 14-15, G-Beaver Bridge, 21GT; 16, View of G-South Branch; 21GT of the G-Mount Misery Brook; 21GT from Beaver Bridge; 17-18, More views of South Branch from Beaver Bridge; 19, G-Five Points; 21GT 1n Lebanon State Forest on same map; 20, G-Five Points; 21GT. gathering
      - Visit to Oriental Food and Gift Shop, Browns Mills, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-008; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-008; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-3, Exteriors of Eugene's Oriental Food and Gift Shop in G-Browns Mills; 21GT; 4, Ray's Sporting Goods Store, next to Eugene's; 5, Exteriors of Eugene's and Ray's; 6-20, Interior shots of Eugene's. Note sign for St. Anne's Catholic Church in both Korean and English (7). Also note picture of Kimberly Eandhait (17) who was later interviewed by Sue Samuelson. ethnicity, foodways
      - Guided tour of portions of New Lisbon, New Jersey, September 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CMH-009; Mary Hufford; PFP-83-CMH-009; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)